<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Publish>
  <ModId Value="77240" />
  <DisplayName Value="Find It" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Find It is a mod that lets you quickly browse and search for all of the assets inside of the game." />
  <LongDescription>
# Find It for Cities: Skylines II
Quickly browse and search through all of the assets inside of the game.
Use **Ctrl+F** to quickly open the Find It panel, or click on the magnifier icon in your toolbar.
Use **Ctrl+P** to enable the Picker tool, or click on the picker icon in your toolbar.

Huge thanks to **YenYang** for their help on the UI.

Special thanks to **Algernon** for their contribution and allowing me to take on this project

Thank you to **Chameleon** for providing the Icons.

And thank you to **Baka-gourd** (NullPinter) for their help with focus.

## Features
* Quick and intelligent search methods.
* Extensive and comprehensive asset categories.
* Panel stays open while placing assets, no jumping between different tabs.
* Tool options like Tree Controller and Line Tool are fully supported and can be used while the panel is open.
* Favorite your most used assets.
* Integrated Picker
* Extensive sorting and filtering options.

## Planned Features
* Mutli-tab support, to have multiple instances open at the same time
* Custom tagging, add your own tags to assets. Will also come with cross compatibility with Skyve.
* Asset information when hovering over an item.

## Notes
Find It should automatically support any mods that add or alter the vanilla assets.

If you're having any issues, please report them on my discord as it's easier to help you that way.
</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot_01.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot_02.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot_03.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot_04.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot_05.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/find-it.1655827" />
  <ModVersion Value="1.1.0" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
  <ChangeLog>
# v1.1.0
## Changes
* Added an Alignment style option, allowing you to position the find it panel on the right of your screen. This comes with its own column and row size option and is saved throughout sessions.
* Added a Building Corner filter, allowing you to search for Left and Right corner buildings, as well as Front-only buildings.
* Added a 'Random' button to select a random asset from the list. This comes with its own hot-key as well, Ctrl+R by default.
* Added a marker next to assets showing that they are placed on the map, you can click this 'Locate' button to find the asset in the map.
* Added a 'Clear Filters' button to easily reset all filters.
* Updated translations.

## UI and UX Improvements
* Arrow keys can now be used to navigate through the list of assets.
* Added theme and pack icons on the right side of assets.
* Fixed the previously selected asset not staying selected after closing and re-opening the find it panel. 
* Fixed changing display styles requiring two clicks to apply.
* Various UI improvements; including better scaling, readability, positioning, and active color fix.
</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/E4k8ZEtRxd" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/JadHajjar/FindIt-CSII" />
  <ExternalLink Type="crowdin" Url="https://crowdin.com/project/find-it-csii" />
  <Dependency Id="74417" />
  <Dependency Id="79634" />
</Publish>